[{"id": 1262, "question": "Have you ever stood side by side with an elephant and touched its ear or its long nose? A marvelous opportunity is offered here for you to experience working with these giant animals. The daily highlight is the walk from the elephant orphanage down to the river to bathe the elephants. Imaging what an amazing fun it is to watch an entire herd splashing around and rolling in the river just feet in front of you! This opportunity is available through a programme designed for visitors and volunteers to work in the world-famous government-run elephant orphanage in Pinnawela, Sri Lanka. The orphanage is regarded as one of the largest centers of its kind in the world, with one of the most successful captive breeding programmes for Asian elephants. Pinnawela Orphanage is situated in the hills of ce...\n\nQ: How many main duties does the passage list for the volunteers?", "options": ["Two.", "Three.", "Four.", "Five."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2287, "question": "From their beginnings New England towns had a special democratic system of government. At a stated time all the citizens would assemble at a town meeting, where they would discuss local problems and express opinions freely. They also elected the town's officials at these gatherings and made decisions about the taxes they would pay and about other community matters. These meetings were usually held at the town hall, which was located in the central square. In the eighteenth-century town meetings, only men who owned property and who were church members actually voted, although everyone present was allowed to express their opinions. Later, all citizens were allowed to vote. Thus the town meeting became truly democratic. Town meetings are still common in New England communities. In recent year...\n\nQ: Why has the town meeting been widely imitated?", "options": ["Because many people are interested in it.", "Because it is very democratic.", "Because many people enjoy themselves at town meetings.", "Because sometimes government agencies call them."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 680, "question": "We're surrounded by chemistry in everyday life. Sometimes it is easy to see, like when your science teacher does a big experiment in class. At other times, it can be pretty hard to see everyday chemistry at work, but nearly everything you touch or use has some element of chemistry in it. Something as simple as toothpaste contains at least three chemicals, if not more. It is the mixture of them and its chemical reaction that keeps your teeth clean. Other things you use every day are created by chemistry, such as hair products, shampoo and soap. Adding detergent to water involves chemistry. Without chemistry, we would never have known that we need soap to get the oil out of clothes or skin. Chemistry not only helps us make products for use, but it also helps us understand the world around us...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Chemistry around the House", "Chemistry in Science", "Chemistry for Dinner", "Chemistry in Everyday Life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3242, "question": "Dr. Paul Kelly, head of Monkeseaton Community High School in North Tyneside, said it would mean the end of sleeping in lessons before lunch, after experiments showed teenagers could have different body clocks from adults and younger children. Russell Foster, an Oxford professor of neuroscience , tested the memory of 200 Monkseaton pupils at 9 am and 2 pm using pairs of words, and discovered a 9% improvement in the afternoon. Students correctly identified 51% of word pairs in the latest session, compared with 42% in the morning. Tayler McCullough, 15, one of the test subjects, said the majority of students would welcome the extra hours in bed, \"I'm extremely hard to get up in the morning. One or two people like to get to school early, but most of us would be up for going in later. I'm sure ...\n\nQ: How many professors are mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2700, "question": "Hubert Joseph Schlafly was an electrical engineer who helped change the way actors, politicians and other people speak on television. In 1950, he and two other men developed the teleprompter. One co-worker, Fred Barton, was an actor. He had an idea for a tool that would help television actors read their lines without having to memorize them. The other co-worker was Irving Kahn. He worked as vice-president of radio and television at 20thCentury Fox. The first teleprompter involved a person who held a long piece of paper printed with big letters. As the actor read the lines, another person would move the paper ahead on the device . The teleprompter was first used on a television program called \"The First Hundred Years.\" Later versions used television screens to show the words that were to be...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["A new form of TV program.", "A great US electrical engineer.", "The influence of an electrical company.", "The history of a useful electrical device."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1930, "question": "Most people believe they don't have imagination. They are wrong. Everyone has imagination, but most of us,once we became adults, forget how to access it. Creativity isn't always connected with great works of art or ideas. People at work and in their free time routinely think of creative ways to solve problems. Maybe you have a goal to achieve,a tricky question to answer or you just want to expand your mind! Here are three techniques to help you. This technique involves taking unrelated ideas and trying to find links between them. First,think about the problem you have to solve or the job you need to do. Then find an image,word,idea or object,for example,a candle. Write down all the ideas/words associated with candles:light,fire,matches, wax,night,silence,etc. Think of as many as you can. T...\n\nQ: The second technique suggests that you just imagine", "options": ["setting a goal is as simple as skiing", "new possibilities will soon appear", "December and January are the best months for skiing.", "you have every resource to achieve your goal"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1182, "question": "Nowadays everybody seems to think that they know English. Many people speak it but few speak it really well. Practice is necessary in speaking English well. Reading is also one of the things that will help you to speak English better. Read whenever you can and whatever you like! Read papers and Internet sites that you like in English every day. Then, you will see that the number of known words is increasing and you are able to speak with more skills. Then you will have made the foundations and a good basis of English. It is not good to stop and get stuck there. Going to England or an English speaking country is a good choice, but many people cannot afford it. If you cannot go, reading and speaking with your friends will also help you to practice your English. However, I think that it is ve...\n\nQ: In the writer's eyes, the essential way to improve your speaking skills is  _  .", "options": ["practicing", "going abroad", "reading", "writing"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2792, "question": "It was 7:00 am in Kyoto, Japan, and the taxi company had just called a second time to say they couldn't find my house. Once again I spelt out directions even a blind person could follow. I glanced impatiently at my watch, and waited. Only two hours remained until my flight left--and it was an hour and a half trip to the airport. Outside, heavy rains were pouring down. My house was so far north in the city that buses pass only here times a day. The telephone rang again. \"Terribly sorry,\" began the man at the taxi company. Then I realized that the taxi company, flooded with calls, could only offer in-city runs. I had heard this happens when the weather gets bad. I shouted into the phone that I had a plane to catch and I would meet the taxi outside my house. Standing in the wind-driven rain, ...\n\nQ: What was the reason for the taxi company not being able to pick him up?", "options": ["More people were riding in taxis on rainy days.", "The writer didn't give the correct address.", "The taxi drivers refused to work.", "The taxi drivers didn't like to drive long distance."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3261, "question": "\"Ten years ago I could never have imagined I'd be doing this,\"says Greg Pal,33,a former software executive. \"I mean ,this is essentially agriculture ,right? But the people I talk to, especially the ones coming out of business school , think this is the one hot area everyone wants to get into .\" He means bugs. To be more accurate, the genetic change of bugs---very, very small ones---so that when they feed on agricultural waste such as woodchip or wheat straw ,they do something extraordinary . They excrete crude oil. Unbelievably ,this is not science fiction .Mr. Pal holds up a small cup of bug excretion that could ,in theory ,be poured into the tank of the big Lexus SUX next to us .Not that Mr. Pal was willing to risk it just yet .He gives it a month before the first vehicle is filled up wi...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Bugs Eat Waste and Excrete Petrol", "Waste Turns into Crude Oil", "A Promising Business", "Software Executive Turned to Bugs"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1598, "question": "One day about 30 years ago, a 2 year-old Chinese boy in Shenyang was watching a Tom and Jerry cartoon on TV. Tom the cat began to play the piano. The music was to beautiful that the boy fell in love with it at once. This little boy was Lang Lang - one of today's great pianists. Lang Lang began to play the piano at 3. By the age of 5, the had won fist place in Shenyang's piano competition and performed his first public recital . People were shocked by his perfect performance and thought he was a real talent. From that time on, playing on the global stage became the dream of Lang Lang and his parents. To help him much closer to his dream, when Lang was 9, his father quit his job and went with Lang to Beijing to help his son study piano. There, Lang did not receive the praise that he had rece...\n\nQ: When did Lang Lang and his father come to Beijing?", "options": ["To hold more concerts", "To perform on the global stage", "To find a good job", "To realize his dream"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2369, "question": "All the oceans of the world will be dead in the future unless action is taken at once. How can this happen? We have already seen that people allow all sorts of waste products to flow into the sea. It is almost impossible to measure how much waste water and industrial waste in our oceans, but we can find out how much oil is poured into them legally and illegally. It is illegal to pour oil into the sea close to the shore, but when a ship is many miles out to sea, there are no such rules. Scientists have different ideas as to the amount of oil putting into the sea, but the lowest figure for oil poured in European waters alone is nearly 200 000 tons every year. Some people say the figure could be ten times as high. It is not only our coasts that suffer from oil pollution. Many shell fish, for ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is WRONG according to the passage?", "options": ["The water body of the earth will be dead by the year 2010 without any effective measure.", "All the Oceans in the world are polluted by oil.", "It's possible that all the creatures in the sea will die out if no action is taken.", "Some kinds of the living things in waters have been poisoned and we must be careful of them."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1994, "question": "On the morning of November 18, 1755, an earthquake shock Boston. John Winthrop, a professor at Harvard College, felt the quake and awoke. \"I rose\", Winthrop wrote, \"and lighted a candle, looked at my watch, and found it to be 15minutes after four.\" John Winthrop hurried downstairs to the grandfather clock. It had stopped three minutes before, at 4:12. Except for stopping the clock, the quake had only thrown a key from the mantel to the floor. The clock had stopped because Winthrop had put some long glass tubes he was using for an experiment into the case for safekeeping. The quake had knocked the tubes over and blocked the pendulum .Winthrop, therefore, had the key on the floor. The quake had thrown _ forward in the direction of the quake' s motion by a shock coming from the northwest, per...\n\nQ: John Winthrop put some tubes into this clock case because  _  .", "options": ["he wanted to do an experiment", "he thought an earthquake was probably to happen soon", "he thought it safe for them to be put there", "he wanted to record the exam time of the earthquake"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2487, "question": "A good friend of mine was complaining about her son the other day.\"Did you notice,\" she started, \"how he didn't wait for me to get my salad before he dove into his?\" True enough, the boy attacked his plate faster than a cat in the wild.Without manners, we're no more than animals.Actually, that's not true.I've been watching and feeding a group of wild cats, and they show unusual politeness toward each other.Even when food is _ , they take turns, leaving at least a small part for the next in line. My mother educated her three children to have good manners all the time.We were made to feel very uncomfortable as if we were sitting on pins and needles until we got used to saying please, thank you, pardon me, and I'm sorry.And I have to say, while it was a painful learning experience, it was one...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that the writer   _  .", "options": ["is surely liked by everyone around her", "is not satisfied with most people's manners around her", "thinks she has been a perfect example to the young", "thanks her mother for teaching her the good manners a lot"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3319, "question": "With five breakout games, Jeremy Lin has become the NBA's newest star. In the New York Knicks' 92-85 won over the Los Angles Lakers last Saturday, Lin had a career-high 38 points.A day later, he led the Knicks to their fifth victory, 100-98 to Minnesota Timberwolves.In his previous games, Lin, 23, had 23 points against the Washington, 25 points against New Jersey and 28 against Utah in his first start. Lin is smart.Before graduating from high school in California, he had sent his application to all the Ivy League Schools .He only got into Harvard and Brown, and he chose Harvard.In 2010, Lin graduated with a degree in economics. Lin is the first Chinese-American player in the NBA.He was born in the US and his family is Asian.Although not born in China, Lin has attracted nearly all Yao Ming'...\n\nQ: From the passage, we learn that    _   .", "options": ["the New York Knicks has never been defeated", "Lin is an American-Chinese basketball player", "most of Yao Ming's fans take Lin as a great role model", "after graduation from Harvard, Lin signed with the Knicks"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1300, "question": "The latest fashion in kitchen is the food steamer. All the stores are selling them; everyone wants one. Steaming is one of the simplest and healthiest ways of cooking food.However, that cooking time is usually longer than with other methods. In case you're thinking of buying a steamer, I've done a survey about the steamers available on the market to help you decide which will suit you best. *Folding Steamer The simplest and least expensive is the folding stainless-steel version. Advantages: This is a good, basic design which sits inside a variety of different shapes of pans with the water under it; a ring in the center allows for easy lifting and it's easy to clean. Disadvantages: It only holds small dishes. Also, if you put too much water in the pan, it will boil up through the vegetables...\n\nQ: The Nutritious Liuing steamer  _  .", "options": ["is more difficult to store", "provides a dish to cook rice with", "cooks different foods at the same time", "cooks fish and chicken faster than vegetables"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 355, "question": "I love everything about making Easter dinner except the Saturday shopping. That day, the supermarket can be as crowded as a department store at Christmas. And this Easter, on top of my regular checklist, I had to buy the ingredient for a delicious, new recipe I'd discovered: sliced ham and turkey layered with Swiss cheese and cabbage, all wrapped in pastry dough. Trouble was that my work schedule had left me no time to shop earlier in the week. I would get up extra early and take care of everything on Saturday morning, I thought, as I drove to the office on Friday. But that morning, Yola, one of my co-workers, asked if my husband Robert and I would help her move the next day. \"I really don't have anybody else to ask,\" she apologized. \"Sure,\" I told her, soft touch that I am. Early Saturday...\n\nQ: Which of the following things surprised the author most?", "options": ["Yola had so much furniture and many boxes to move.", "Yola gave her so much food to express her thanks.", "Yola had known what she was in need of.", "Yola gave her exactly what she wanted to buy."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2561, "question": "Black has long been praised for its ability to better women's figures and suit every occasion. But the color has a side-effect--it ages the face. While black does give the appearance of a slimmer figure by making the shadows less visible, wearing it next to the face brings out a negative effect. Black clothing can highlight dark lines under the chin, shadows around the eyes and wrinkles on the face. The effect can be as serious as making women feel exhausted, self-conscious and upset. Wrinkles and sunken areas appear deeper and more pronounced, meaning the effect is more obvious in older women. Dark scarves, hats and high-collared coats are apparently particularly likely to emphasize aging features of the face. But fear not. The effect can be _ by a splash of color around the neck--in the ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, wearing black clothes probably   _  .", "options": ["makes the wearer less energetic", "gives away the wearer's age", "darkens the wearer's skin tone", "makes the wearer feel confident"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1828, "question": "September is an exciting month in every college freshman's life. For many, it's the first time that they've left home to live in a new environment. But after the hustle and bustle of a few weeks, excitement gives way to a less enjoyable emotion-- homesickness. Homesickness manifests itself in many ways. You may miss mum's cooking, your pets, or even your old bed. All this becomes a fond memory of the past. Homesickness can be a bitter feeling for many students, especially when faced with the challenges of settling into an unfamiliar environment. But remember, you're not alone. According to a recent BBC article, 70 percent of British college students experience homesickness. In this increasingly globalized world in which people migrate to faraway places for a relationship, education or work...\n\nQ: The attitude of Sedikides towards homesickness is   _  .", "options": ["negative", "supportive", "skeptical", "critical"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1683, "question": "It was a warm April day when a big fat envelope came in the mail from the only college I had ever imagined attending. I tore open the packet. My eyes were fixed on the word \"congratulations. \"I don't remember ever smiling so wide. Then I looked at my financial package. The cost of Dream School's tuition , room and board was around $ 40,000- an impossible sum! How could I afford to attend? What good reasons did I have to go there when three other fine colleges were offering me free tuition? My other choices were good, solid schools even if they weren't as famous as my first choice. In my mind, attending my dream university would be the only way to realize my dream of becoming a world-class writer. My parents understood how I felt. They told me that even though it would be a financial proble...\n\nQ: What does the author mainly want to say?", "options": ["You should consider comfort in your choice of schools.", "You should try your best to attend your dream school.", "Your second-choice college may actually by your best fit.", "Your choice of schools should be based on their fame."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1480, "question": "A person named Bernard Jackson today is a free man, but he has many bitter memories. He spent five years in prison after a jury wrongly convicted (...) him of raping two women. At Jackson's trial, although two witnesses testified that Jackson was with them in another location at the time of the crime, he was convicted anyway. Why? The jury believed the testimony of the two victims, who positively identified Jackson as the man who had attacked them. The court eventually freed Jackson after the police found the real criminal. Many factors influence the accuracy of eyewitness testimony. For instance, witnesses sometimes see photographs of several suspects before they try to identify the person they saw in a group of people. They can become confused by seeing many photographs of similar faces....\n\nQ: Eyewitness testimony is important because    _   .", "options": ["it can be relied on to detect criminals in all cases.", "it is sometimes the only way to resolve court cases.", "it is sometimes the only clue for police investigation.", "it is more reliable than physical evidences to a crime."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 868, "question": "To Whom It May Concern: prefix = st1 /Chengdu #7 High School is proud to send an Odyssey of the MindTeam to World Competition this year. They competed inShanghaifor the National Competition and were selected to go to World. The World Competition will be held at the University of Maryland in theUnited Statesat the end of May. Odyssey of the Mind is a creative problem-solving competition. Teams of up to seven students will solve a complex problem using innovative ideas and materials. They will be judged on originality in three separate categories. Odyssey of the Mind competitions emphasize team work and creative \"out of the box\" solutions. The strength of this program is that the solutions are the work of the students only - neither coaches nor parents are allowed input. During the competiti...\n\nQ: This passage is actually   _  .", "options": ["an application", "a document", "a website", "a letter"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1693, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time. _ Verona De Tessant (Maya Rudolph) and Burt Farlander (John Krasinski) are in their early thirties and struggling to meet daily needs and build fulfilling lives as an artist and a salesman. When they learn they will soon become parents, they are faced with the challenge of how and where to raise a child and build a happy family. With a baby on his way, the young couple, look at their lives and are puzzled about what they really want. _ Lynn was married to Pual, but they broke up and Lynn took their daughter Alice while Paul got their son Dylan. Years later, now Dylan is getting married, and Lynn is attending the wedding, with her younger son Elliot and Ben. Elliot is a drug...\n\nQ: Which film might best help a newly married couple to figure out their new roles in future life?", "options": ["La Vita e bella", "Another Happy Day", "Away We Go", "The Shawshank Redemption."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1220, "question": "The word I'm going to introduce to you today is-phubbing. Let's see the definition of this term:phubbing n. the act of snubbing someone in a social setting by looking at your cell phone instead of paying attention As you can probably guess, phubbing is a blend of phone and snubbing. The term was coined by a 23-year-old Melbourne resident Alex Haigh. Obviously, he got fed up with how people are always checking Facebook or Twitter on their phones when they are supposed to be interacting with someone face to face. He wanted to put an end to this social phenomenon, therefore he came up with this catchy term. And it did catch on. The word's earliest media mention dates back to June 2012, and in a little over a year's time, phubbing has already been picked up by almost all the mainstream media o...\n\nQ: The writer suggests we should   _  .", "options": ["stop phubbing in public places", "not be afraid of the harmful effect", "be brave to support a st ranger phubbing", "remind our friends of Stop Phubbing campaign"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2567, "question": "Ten years ago,Morgan Zuch,a two--year--old girl from Long Island,New York,was diagnosed with leukemia .The day that Morgan's father Rod knew it,he made a promise,\"If my daughter gets better,I will devote the rest of my life to helping others who are in the Same condition.\" Fortunately.Morgan recovered gradually,and since then,Rod and his wife Nancy,have been helping other families with cancer.stricken children through the Morgan Center.It is the country's first preschool for children with cancer. Because of the risk of germs, children with cancer are usually forbidden from playing with other kids.They must spend their days in hospital rooms or lying in bed at home.The Zuchs believed that children with cancer should have the opportunity to play,too. The center offers the kids and their fami...\n\nQ: This text is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["Long Island's first preschool for kids with cancer", "the pain that the kids in the Morgan Center suffer", "the contributions Morgan has made to the Center", "the Zuchs,the creators of the Morgan Center"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1817, "question": "I want to tell you a story that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Saturday morning. We decided to stop at a local restaurant to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as though he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something warm to drink; however, it was not this that I remember, because that is not what \"moved\" me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog owner, I knew that the dog was a mother, and that she had just had some pups . She was hungry and weak and I felt...\n\nQ: Which of the following moved the author?", "options": ["The homeless man had no money to buy food for himself.", "The homeless man wore worn clothes on cold days.", "The homeless man bought food for a dog with all his money.", "Most people walking by the dog didn't notice her."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3359, "question": "When American inventor Alexander Graham Bell invented the telephone in 1876, it was a revolution in communication. For the first time, people could talk to each other over great distances. Over the last two decades a new means of spoken communication has appeared: the mobile phone. The mobile phone is like a two-way radio. But the two-way radio is a limited means of communication. As soon as the users move out of range of each other's broadcast area, the signal is lost. In the 1940s, researchers experimented with the idea of using a number of radio masts to pick up signals from two-way radios. A caller would always be within range of one of the masts. When he or she moved too far away from one mast, the next mast would pick up the signal. (Scientists referred to each mast's reception area ...\n\nQ: The last sentence of the whole passage ''That's gr8!  But I'm v busy rite now. Will call U 2nite.\" May probably means  _  .", "options": ["That's great! But I'm very busy right now. (I) Will call you tonight", "It's eight now. I'm very busy. (I) Will call you tonight", "That's great! But I'm busy writing now. (I) Will call you at two tonight", "\"8\" is great! But I'm very busy right now. (I) Will call it \"U\" tonight"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1963, "question": "Every year, Americans send millions of tons of food to the landfill . What if you could use all of those rotten vegetables to heat your home? That's happening in one unlikely laboratory: the Newtown Creek Wastewater Treatment Plan in Brooklyn The plant's longtime manager, Jimmy Pynn, shows off the plant's crown jewels: eight huge, shiny, oval-shaped steel tanks known as digester eggs. Each one contains millions of gallons of black material that's roughly pea soup. Pynn calls it \"black gold\". \"The digesters like to be fed like us: three times a day,\" he says. \"They like to be kept warm, 98 degrees. And that's what we have these guys for: to make methane ,which can be used to heat homes or make electricity.\" Right now, what these bacteria are digesting is mostly sewage mud. But they are bein...\n\nQ: The tone of the last sentence is  _  .", "options": ["humorous", "suggestive", "regretful", "curious"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1812, "question": "A 13-year-old American boy on Saturday became the youngest climber to conquer Mount Everest, the world's highest mountain. Jordan Romero from Big Bear, California, climbed up the 8,850-meter summit from the Tibetan side. On the same day, a Nepali man, Apa Sherpa, broke his own world record of climbing Everest when he reached the summit for the twentieth time. Apa Shepa's team set off from Nepal's capital, Kathmandu, last month, heading for the base camp on the Chinese side of the mountain. \"The team has just called in and believe that they are standing on top of Mt. Everest,\" Romero's blog said. \"Their dreams have now come true. Everyone is happy.\" The climbing has put Romero one step closer to reaching his goal of climbing the highest mountains on all seven continents . \"It is just a goal...\n\nQ: Why did Jordan Romero choose to climb from the Chinese side of Mount Everest?", "options": ["China allows climbers of any age to climb Mt. Everest.", "It wasn't far from Jordan's base camp on the Chinese side.", "There were more challenges on the Chinese side.", "There were more local guides on the Chinese side."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1964, "question": "Here is some general information about Edison Elementary School. For more information, you can visit our website which is printed on the cover. Attendance: Please contact the office at 480. 472. 5282 if your child is going to be absent. Renaissance Reading: The Accelerated Reader (AR) Program is a computerized reading enrichment program that combines great children's literature with computer skills. As an individualized reading program, it is designed to motivate students to read more and to read good literature. Students of different abilities can use this program. It is not a competitive program but one that improves any student's reading ability. Here is how it works. Students select books in their reading range from our Accelerated Reader Selection and read it at their own pace. Once t...\n\nQ: The passage may be selected from   _  .", "options": ["a magazine", "a newspaper", "a website", "a novel"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2435, "question": "May 28 (Reuters Life!) - A Japanese university is giving away Apple Inc's (AAPL.O) trendy iPhone to students for free, but with a catch: the device will be used to check their attendance. The project, which is being tested ahead of its formal launch in June, involves 550 first and second year students and some staff of a department at Aoyama Gakuin University, which is located just outside Tokyo in Sagamihara city. The school's iPhones are meant to create a mobile information network between students and professors, but they are also a convenient way for the teachers to take attendance in class. As students enter the room, instead of writing their name on a sheet, they simply type in their ID number and a specific class number into an iPhone application. To prevent students from logging in...\n\nQ: Teachers at Aoyama Gakuin University can finish taking attendance by asking students to  _", "options": ["write their names on the paper", "Type in their ID and class numbers into iphone", "log in from home or outside class ahead", "put in right GPS location data and their router"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3465, "question": "Choosing the Right Resolution Millions of Americans began 2014 with the same resolution they started 2013 with, a goal of losing weight. However, setting weight loss as a goal is a mistake. To reach our goal of losing weight --- the output, we need to control what we eat --- the input ( ). That is, we tend to care about the output but not to control the input. This is a bad way to construce goals. The alternative is to focus your resolution on the input. Instead of resolving to lose weight, try an actionable resolution: \"I'll stop having desert for lunch,\" or \"I'll walk every day for 20 minutes.\" Creating a goal that focuses on a well-specified input will likely be more effective than concentrating on the outcome. Recently a new science behind incentives , including in education, has been ...\n\nQ: According to the writer, which of the following statements is a good goal?", "options": ["\"I'll give up desert.\"", "\"I'll study harder.\"", "\"I'll cut down my expense\"", "\"I'll spend more time with my family\""], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3062, "question": "China, known as the \"kingdom of bicycle\", will see a quick growth in electric bicycle production in the next five years thanks to the country's efforts to save energy and improve the environment. The output of electric bikes is expected to maintain an annual growth rate of at least 80 percent in the coming five years. China will _ 30 million electricity-driven bikes in 2020, compared to 9 million bikes last year, according to a report from the Development Research Center under the State Council and other ministries such as the National Development and Reform Commission. The central government wants to reduce the amount of energy consumption by as much as 20 percent within the next five years. That would be achieved through the introduction of new sources of energy and encouraging people to...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to make electric bicycles", "The world's biggest producer of electric bicycles", "China's quick growth in electric bicycle", "How to save energy and improve the environment"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3032, "question": "Are you a big fan of pirate stories? Do you know how to talk like a pirate? You can have fun on September 19th. This special holiday is called International Talk Like A Pirate Day. It was invented in 1995 by two young Americans, John Baur and Mark Summers. These two good friends came up with this idea when they were playing racquetball, and began to talk like pirates. At that moment, they thought, \"Young people are interested in pirate, but there is no such a chance for people to get together to share it. Why not have a day when everybody talks like a pirate?\" They decided to make September 19th the date. Since then, Baur and Summers have tried hard to promote Talk Like A Pirate Day. As Baur said, \"We've talked like pirates, and encouraged several of our friends to do so every September 19...\n\nQ: How did John Baur and Mark Summers invent the special holiday?", "options": ["Many young people asked them to do it", "They did it just for pleasure", "They did it in order to honor pirates", "They thought out the idea by chance and imagination"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 788, "question": "When Chinese student Du Juan brought her American boyfriend home two years ago to use the toilet, her Japanese roommate became so upset that she shouted in English: \"I hate you.\" Du, then 21 and an undergraduate at Bridgewater State College in Massachusetts, was shocked. So was her boyfriend. \"Later I realized that she didn't literally mean what she said and that she was not aware of the full meaning of the word 'hate' in English,\" said Du. \"It was more a problem with translation,\" she added. Cultural differences can cause confusion about what words or even actions mean, an issue that has come to the forefront recently following the arrest of a Chinese doctoral degree student in New Jersey. Zhai Tiantian, who studied at the Stevens Institute of Technology, has been accused of trying to set...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Du Juan's unpleasant experience abroad.", "Confusion caused by translation.", "Conservational skills in a foreign country.", "Cultural differences between China and America."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2543, "question": "Music for Humans and Humpback Whales As researchers conclude in Science, the love of music is not only a universal feature of the human species, but is also deeply fixed in complex structures of the human brain, and is far more ancient than previously suspected. In the articles that discuss the field of bio-musicology, the study of the biological basis for the creation and appreciation of music, researchers present various evidence to, show that music-making is at once an original human \"business\", and an art form with skillful performers throughout the animal kingdom. The new reports stress that humans hold no copyright on sound wisdom, and that a number of nonhuman animals produce what can rightly be called music, rather than random sound. Recent in-depth analyses of the songs sung by hu...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the article?", "options": ["Animals are able to compose and enjoy music like humans.", "Human beings borrow ideas in music from humpback whales.", "Humpback whales are skillful performers in the animal kingdom.", "Music-making, an ancient activity of both humans and animals."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1536, "question": "When I left my bag on a train, I lost my most precious possession, a small framed photograph of my great grandparents, Emily and Gordon Baker. The frame was made of silver, with an elegant flower design in one corner. The photograph was taken in March 1939 on their wedding day. Emily looked very happy, and Gordon looked rather alarmed. A few months later, he was killed in action in North Africa. I received the photograph when my aunt Mabel died. I'm a student at Edinburgh University and I live in an old Edwardian house. At the end of last term, I packed a large bag and a small bag and set off for London, where I was planning to catch the Eurostar train to Paris. Minutes after getting off the train at Kings Cross Station, I realized that I'd left the small bag in the overhead luggage rack. ...\n\nQ: The author's most precious possession was   _    .", "options": ["A wedding photo in a silver frame taken in North Africa", "A pretty family portrait in a silver frame taken in 1939", "A special photo of his great grandparents in a silver frame", "A common photograph of his grandparents taken by Mabel"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 320, "question": "Cutting global warming pollution would not only make the planet healthier, it would make people healthier too, new research suggested. Cutting carbon dioxide emissions could save millions of lives, mostly by reducing preventable deaths from heart and lung diseases, according to studies released Wednesday and published in a special issue of The Lancet, a British medical journal. \"Relying on fossil fuels leads to unhealthy lifestyles, increasing our chances of getting sick and in some cases takes years from our lives,\" US Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius said in a telecast briefing from her home state of Kansas. \"As greenhouse gas emissions go down, so do deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. This is not a small effect.\" Instead of looking at the health il...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the most practical way to cut carbon dioxide emissions according to the passage?   _  .", "options": ["Driving less", "Walking and cycling as much as possible.", "Stopping using fossil fuels", "Reducing the use of polluting fuels to cook."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2499, "question": "Have you ever wanted to feel like you were in a western film? Or maybe you wanted to feel like you were a pioneer traveling the west? It is possible to experience such things during a Wild West vacation! Here are four of the best Wild West vacation locations available: Walk the Lewis and Clark Trail Walk some or all of the 3,700 miles trail that was traversed by Mariwether Lewis and William Clark, two of the world's greatest explorers. Though not all the trails are marked, there are various stops that have been preserved by various historic societies. There is also a coach that makes a 16-day _ following the trail. This begins in St. Louis, Missouri, and ends in Astoria, Oregon. Venture Route 66 Take a tour or go to see it yourself -- ride on the famous Route 66. The road is nearly 2,500 m...\n\nQ: What do we know from the passage?", "options": ["A number of historic stops aren't protected well.", "William Clark was a pioneer who explored the west.", "Western films are the most popular among Americans.", "None of the trails in the west are marked."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3283, "question": "Nigel received a reward for his excellence in study. It began when he was selected to help the teachers in the computer laboratories. The peak of his school career came not when he topped the school but when he was selected for the nationwide competition. Unlike everyone else, Nigel wanted to join the contest because he liked making something out of the Lego sets. Nigel spent the next two months rebuilding the robot. It was during the time that Nigel found out about the prizes for the competition as well as another competitor, Alicia, from a neighboring school. His early intentions were forgotten. Getting the thousand-dollar prize was more important than anything else. Nigel decided to befriend Alicia. Unaware of his intentions, she told him all about the robot that she had been building f...\n\nQ: Nigel's original intention of joining the contest was to   _  .", "options": ["be the top student of the school", "constructs a robot with the Lego sets", "being great honor to his school", "wins the thousand-dollar prize"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3284, "question": "Nigel received a reward for his excellence in study. It began when he was selected to help the teachers in the computer laboratories. The peak of his school career came not when he topped the school but when he was selected for the nationwide competition. Unlike everyone else, Nigel wanted to join the contest because he liked making something out of the Lego sets. Nigel spent the next two months rebuilding the robot. It was during the time that Nigel found out about the prizes for the competition as well as another competitor, Alicia, from a neighboring school. His early intentions were forgotten. Getting the thousand-dollar prize was more important than anything else. Nigel decided to befriend Alicia. Unaware of his intentions, she told him all about the robot that she had been building f...\n\nQ: What reward did Nigel receive for doing well in his school work?", "options": ["He helped in the computer laboratories", "He was honored with a scholarship", "He helped his teacher construct a robot", "He was offered a part-time job"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 705, "question": "During the tsunami disaster of 2004, over 300,000 people died. No one has counted the number of animals killed, but we know that it wasn't many. All over the region, before the disaster struck, animals were behaving strangely. Shortly before the tsunami, in Khaolak, Thailand, twelve elephants that were giving tourists rides became agitated. They suddenly left their usual habitat, carrying four surprised Japanese tourists to safety. On the eastern coast of India, flamingos , which should be breeding at this time of year, suddenly flew to higher ground. Of the two thousand wild pigs that live in an Indian nature reserve, only one was found dead after the tsunami. The idea that the animals are able to predict disasters is nothing new. In fact, it has been well-recorded over the years. Twelve ...\n\nQ: The wild animals can predict the natural disasters because they   _  .", "options": ["can run for their lives when natural disasters happen", "don't even have the modern technology to help them", "are being observed and tracked for scientific experiments", "are quick to notice the slightest changes in the environment"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2169, "question": "Mark Twain left school when he was twelve. He had little school education. In spite of this, he became the most famous writer of his time. He made millions of dollars by writing. His real name was Samuel Langhorne Clemens, but he is better known to all over the world as Mark Twain, his penname. Mark Twain was born in 1835 and he was not a healthy baby. In fact, he was not expected to live through the first winter. But with his mother's care, he managed to survive. As a boy, he caused much trouble for his parents. He used to play jokes on all his friends and neighbors. He didn't like to go to school, and he often ran away from home. He always went in the direction of the nearby Mississippi. He was nearly drowned nine times. After his father's death, Mark Twain began to work for a printer, w...\n\nQ: In Mark Twain's childhood,   _  .", "options": ["he learned a lot at school", "his mother often worried about his safety", "he often went swimming with other boys", "he often played games with other boys"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 499, "question": "Every spring Beijing is choked by huge sandstorms.The sky turns a strange and frightening yellow colour as clouds of sand sweep down from the deserts of Mongolia and north-western China.Strong winds blow up the dust and cover everything in sight--in 2006,a storm dumped 330,000 tonnes of dust on Beijing in one night. The number of sandstorms has grown alarmingly over the years as the deserts have expanded.This is partly man-made and partly because of climate .Many grasslands have been overgrazed by sheep and goats,or ploughed up,leaving the soil dangerously exposed.Too much water has been taken out of rivers,and the situation is made worse by increasingly long-lasting droughts that have affected the northern half of China as the climate grows warmer and drier.The result is probably the wors...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the huge programme\"the Great Green Wall\"?", "options": ["To protect the Great Wall.", "To plant as many trees as possible along the Great Wall.", "To stop the deserts from moving towards Beijing.", "To plant as many trees as possible in Beijing."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 599, "question": "Poet William Stafford once said that we are defined more by the detours in life than by the narrow road toward goals.I like this image.But it was quite by accident that I discovered the deep meaning of his words. For years we made the long drive from our home in Seattle to my parents' home in Boise in nine hours.We traveled the way most people do:the fastest,shortest,easiest road,especially when I was alone with four noisy,restless kids who hate confinement and have strong opinions about everything. Road trips felt risky,so I would drive fast,stopping only when I had to.We would stick to the freeways and arrive tired. But then Banner,our lamb was born.He was rejected by his mama days before our planned trip to Boise.I had two choices:leave Banner with my husband,or take him with me.My husb...\n\nQ: What could be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Charm of the Detour", "The Road to Bravery", "Creativity out of Necessity", "Road Trip and Country Life"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1606, "question": "Security Services advise that there have been robberies reported in the East Oxford area, carried out by a group and involving threats of and showing of a knife.The victims have all been young males of student age and appearance who have been walking alone between 7 pm and the early hours of the morning.Some of the victims have been followed from the O2 and the Regal Hotel. The Crime Prevention Advisor offers the following advice: *If possible walk home in a group, not on your own.If someone tries to take something from you by force, it may be best to give it to them, this way it will avoid you getting injured. *If someone tries to follow you, make for a public place, such as a shop or a restaurant or walk towards other people.Make lots of noise and use your personal alarm to shock the per...\n\nQ: Where does this text probably come from?", "options": ["Traffic regulations.", "An advertisement.", "A news report.", "A university website."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1575, "question": "\"Humans have a code of ethics ,\" says Marc Bekoff, an animal behavior expert at the University of Colorado. \" If I don't play in a certain way, you won't play with me. Some animals have the same code.\" Scientists recently discovered that animals that live in groups, such as elephants, foxes, and wolves, are especially likely to follow rules. If they don't, and each does its own thing, the group might break apart. Group members would be forced to live alone. Then they'd have a harder time hunting and raising their young. That's probably why a traveling wolf pack stopped and waited to let its slowly moving leader catch up. Similar social ties may have caused a captive elephant to save her friend from drowning. Selfish reasons certainly motivated the male fox, who wanted to keep playing. Some...\n\nQ: Why are animals who live in groups especially likely to follow rules?", "options": ["Because they can make an easier living in that way.", "Because they can have a harder time hunting in that way.", "Because they can keep playing with each other.", "Because they can save their friends from danger."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1471, "question": "Wal-Mart is not just the world's largest retailer . It's the world's largest company, which sells in three months what number-two retailer Home Depot sells in a year. Wal-Mart exercises its power for just one purpose: to bring the lowest possible prices to its customers. At Wal-Mart, that goal is never reached. The retailer has a clear policy for suppliers: On basic products that don't change, the price Wal-Mart will pay, and will charge shoppers, must drop year after year. But what almost no one outside the world of Wal-Mart and none of its 21,000 suppliers know is the high cost of those low prices. To survive in the face of its pricing demands, makers of everything from bikes to jeans have had to close US plants in favor of obtaining products from abroad. Indeed, the real story of Wal-Ma...\n\nQ: Wal-Mart's low price policy results in   _  .", "options": ["more high-paying jobs", "better designed packages", "bigger profit of its partners", "more jobless American workers"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3447, "question": "Study Books Basic Study Manual Hardcover :$ 37 Future success depends on the ability to learn. Here are the answers to the questions most often asked by parents, teachers, business trainers and by students themselves. Read this book and learn: What the three barriers to study are and what to do about them. What to do if you get tired of a subject you are studying. Twenty-six simple drills to help you learn how to study easily, rapidly and with full understanding. Buy and read Basic Study Manual and use it do dramatically improve your ability to study. Study Skills for Life Hardcover: $32 L. Ron Hubbard's study technology for children opens the door to their future success by giving them the ability to study and learn. Fully illustrated (,) for easy comprehension. Learning How to Learn Hard...\n\nQ: If you buy the four books on April 30, 2014, you will have to pay   _   for them.", "options": ["$ 130", "$ 112", "$ 65", "$ 18"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1377, "question": "Facebook users may feel socially successful in the web world but they are more likely to perform poorly in exams. The majority of students who use Facebook every day are doing badly compared with those who don't. About 83% of British 16 to 24-year-old people are using social networking site such as Facebook and MySpace, to keep in touch with friends and organize their social activities. \"Our study shows people who spend more time on Facebook spend less time studying,\" said Aryn Karpinski, a researcher. \"Every generation has its distractions , but I think Facebook is a unique phenomenon.\" Karpinski and a colleague questioned 219 US undergraduates and graduates about their study and general Internet use, as well as their specific use of Facebook. They found 65% of Facebook users accessed the...\n\nQ: Why did Daisy Jones deactivate her account?", "options": ["She was warned about the risk of using Facebook.", "Spending much time on Facebook affected her study", "She wanted to write a long article in the library.", "There was something wrong with her eyes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1121, "question": "Last week, I bought an alarm system for about $ 450. It consisted of a control unit with three other small units. I put the control unit in the sitting room and fastened the other units by the front door, back door and living-room windows. The instructions told us to choose three numbers, so we chose 491, the last three numbers of our telephone number. Now I must explain how the alarm works: 1. There is a power siren in the control unit. It makes a very loud noise. 2. Each of the small units sends out beams or rays in different directions. If anything moves, it breaks a beam. This sends a signal to the control unit. The siren makes a noise that you can hear 50 meters away. 3. When we go to bed, I press the three buttons numbered 4, 9 and 1. Then we have 30 seconds to get out of the room be...\n\nQ: The purpose of the three units was to  _  .", "options": ["send a message to the control unit and start the siren", "sound their own sirens when the control unit told them to", "check that the control unit worked properly all the time", "give them enough light"], "answer": 0}]